{
    "subject": "Sophia_Magdalena_of_Denmark",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Gustav_III_of_Sweden",
    "human_readable": "Sophia Magdalena of Denmark is married to Gustav III of Sweden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9569883942604065,
            "question": "Who was Sophia Magdalena of Denmark married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9178693294525146,
            "question": "Who was Gustav III of Sweden married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8065792322158813,
            "question": "What is the name of the king who was married to Sophia Magdalena of Denmark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8040679693222046,
            "question": "What is the name of the queen who was married to Gustav III of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8040235638618469,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the relationship between Sophia Magdalena and Gustav III?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7130274176597595,
            "question": "To which country did Sophia Magdalena of Denmark belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6655339598655701,
            "question": "What was the role of Sophia Magdalena in Swedish history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6445228457450867,
            "question": "Was Sophia Magdalena of Denmark a queen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46923667192459106,
            "question": "Was Gustav III of Sweden a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15270863473415375,
            "question": "Which two countries are involved in this marriage relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sophia Magdalena of Denmark is married to Gustav III of Sweden.",
            "html": "yago_30024_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Gustav III of Sweden a king?",
            "html": "yago_30024_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Sophia Magdalena of Denmark a queen?",
            "html": "yago_30024_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the role of Sophia Magdalena in Swedish history?",
            "html": "yago_30024_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30024_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Sophia Magdalena of Denmark was the wife of King Gustav III of Sweden, and that they were married in 1766. They also provide details about their marriage, children, and life together, which confirms the correctness of the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear evidence that Sophia Magdalena of Denmark was married to Gustav III of Sweden. For instance, multiple documents mention their marriage in 1766 and her becoming the Queen consort of Sweden upon his ascension to the throne."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}